Temitope Odeyemi

Graphic Designer

Energetic and self-motivated graphic artist with over 7+ years of experience, seeking a job in a prestigious organization searching for a high-level designer to improve their team. Understand new developments in marketing and production approaches to develop the most responsive and functional multi-purpose projects.



WORK EXPERIENCE

Sr. Graphic Designer

Printzilla Inc.

March 2020 to January 2021

Successfully manage and coordinate graphic design projects from concept to completion. Work directly with clients to develop vision, conceive designs and consistently meet deadlines and requirements. Efficiently create, motivate, and direct design and production teams. Create and deliver good persuasive sales and marketing presentations.

Jr. Graphic Designer

Vakoot Print Ventures

January 2015 to March 2016

Created new marketing and collateral design themes. Collaborate with the creative team to design and create computer-generated artwork for advertising and sales materials. Participated in the production of print and promotional items for key customers under the direction of the Advertising Department.

Freelance Graphic Designer

Offline and Online (i.e Fiverr.com)

November 2014 to Present

Designed over 100 popular start-up logos, UI/UX, and other graphic related jobs mainly across Europe, Asia, Africa and North America. Collaborated with the start-up business to create an unique brand. Participated in hundreds of design competitions on 99 designs. Being able to work under pressure and to submit excellent designs before the deadline.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree in Visual Art and Communication Design

Eastern Mediterranean University- Northern, Cyprus.

September 2018 to Present

Ordinary National Diploma in Graphic Design

Don Bosco Technical School- Akure, Nigeria.

February 2013 to November 2014

PORTFOLIO

https://temitope.design

SKILLS

Graphic Design

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe InDesign

Branding

Typography

UI/UX (Adobe XD, Figma and Sketch)

Presentation Skills

Photography

Oral and Written Commnication

Proficiency in English Language
